<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PivotMario</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PivotMario</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Track Record</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/track-record/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/track-record/</guid>
      <description>Legacy System Revamp at 50Hertz&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;At 50Hertz, the transmission system operator, I am involved in transforming a legacy accounting platform that managed critical energy settlement processes. Their system is 90s code, largely undocumented, and based on outdated Java, posing several challenges:&#xA;The system was a black box—users had no visibility into the processes and calculations, implemented in the 30+ years of usage Team inefficiencies and hierarchical structures hindered progress, a poor feedback process and resentment towards the lead of the team Solution: We introduced automated process modeling using Neo4J, which allowed us to visualize previously hidden database relationships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 15:53:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about-me/</guid>
      <description>About Me&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Mario, a passionate and enthusiastic business process specialist currently working for 50Hertz, one of Germany&amp;rsquo;s energy grid operators. My journey in the world of business analysis and process optimization has been full of twists and to me is a journey of continuied learning from and for the purpose.&#xA;My Role at 50Hertz&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;At my current role as a Business Analyst in a eight-head software dev team, where we&amp;rsquo;re on a mission to transform the way we manage energy grid settlement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 21:12:41 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Me&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Please fill out the form below to get in touch with me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resume/</guid>
      <description>Mario André&amp;rsquo;s Resume&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Summary&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Business Analyst with extensive experience in helping product owners by detailing out tickets and tasks. Skilled in project management, data analysis, and communication.&#xA;Experience&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Senior Business Analyst&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Company Name, Location&#xA;Dates of Employment&#xA;Detailed out tasks and tickets for product owners. Managed project timelines and deliverables. Conducted data analysis to support business decisions. Business Analyst&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Company Name, Location</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
